

Javier Giordano
Data Scientist
Diseñador Multimedia
Web Dev - Digital Artist

Teléfono: 1559301321

E-Mail: javiergiordano@gmail.com

Web:

http://javiergiordano.com.ar/

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/javier-

giordano-789648174



## **PFRFII**

I am a Data Scientist with a strong business vision, currently focused on digital transformation,

proactive, curious and a fan of cybersecurity, artificial vision and IA. I really enjoy researching and learning new technologies to find creative solutions to new challenges.

I consider myself passionate about technology and knowing how the world works, I like to investigate and that is why throughout my career I was able to develop myself in different areas, which allows me to have a comprehensive view of things (I am an eternal student).



# **EDUCATION**

2019	Data Science Career (ACAMICA Inst).
2019	Python for computer vision OpenCV and Deep Learning.
2019	Python for data science and Machine Learning bootcamp.
2018	Machine Learning and Business Intelligence (f. telefónica).
2018	Fundamentals of Computer Hacking.
2018	Responsive Web Development.
2009-2012	Diseño Multmedial (Escuela Davinci)



# WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 -2021 HSBC Data visualization. Interactive data dashboard for internal management of the transformation team

- Made with D3.js DC.js Crossfilter.js

2019 - Act. DameLuna Chief executive. Commercial management and asset management, comprehensive digital

 $transformation, corporate\ identity,\ digital\ ecosystem,\ marketing\ plan,\ e-commerce\ development.$ 

2018 La Vía Campesina, Front-end Dev. Design and development of educational platform and interactive content

With geolocation.

2017 **Picker**, **Digital Marketing and communication manager**. E-commerce development – MercadoLibre integration,

Social media marketing planner.

2002 La Mar en Coche, Freelance, Web design/Dev – Interactive design, technical operator – Motion capture based

games design for social events.

2011 - 2015 Ministerio de Planifcación Federal, inversión pública y Servicios, Team Leader, Theatrical and multimedia

content creator for public activities.



#### SKILLS

#### IT

Python
JavaScript - D3.js
Data Analysis - ETL - Viz
Tableau - Carto
OpenCV - AI
Deep/Machine Learning

## Web

HTML5 CSS3 Three.js Bootstrap Moodle

### Diseño

Photoshop - Illustrator Blender - Cinema 4D A/V Adobe Afer Efects Premiere

# **Extras**

Inglés B1
Unity 3D
Cibersecurity/hacking
Realtme Signal Processing
Creatve Coding